

NUR SUHANA OOI

920407-07-5170

MARKETING & HUMAN RESOURCE **POSITION**

EMAIL

suhanaooi7744@gmail.com

ADDRESS

No 114, Lorong Meranti 4, Taman Meranti. 09000 Kulim, Kedah Darul Aman.

PHONE NUMBER

012-534 2890

ABOUT ME

I am 26 years old and live in Kulim, Kedah. I have 3 siblings. I have a degree in Marketing. Although I haven't had any working experience internship, I am a fast learner, like to work in a team and able to finish my work on time besides have a positive attitude and can work under pressure.

SKILLS	
MS Office	••••
MS Power Point	••••
MS Excel	••••

LANGUAGES	
Malay	••••
English	• • • •

WORK EXPERIENCES



Dec 2011 - May 2012

INTERNSHIP STUDENT BERTAM PROPERTIES SDN.BHD

- Responsible to handle customer problem.
- Disseminate information about properties to the public.
- Attract people to buy the properties.



Jun 2013 - Sep 2013

CUSTOMER SERVICE DAILY FRESH FOODS SDN.BHD

- Food preparation.
- Interact with the customer and approach them to buy.



Sep 2013 - Feb 2014

OFFICE ADMINISTRATION HEMI-COLO RECREATION SDN.BHD

- Handling recruitment activities such as screening resumes, coordinating interview arrangement.
- Make a schedule for the workers.
- Collect their attendance form.



Sep 2017 - Jan 2018

INTERNSHIP STUDENT

RUZA RESOURCES MANUFACTURING SDN.BHD

- Responsible to handle customer complaints.
- Disseminate information about the products to customer.
- Need to interact with the customer and persuade them to buy the products.

HOBBIES







Reading Traveling Open Website

EDUCATION & SEMINAR/WORKSHOP ATTENDED



Feb 2014 - Jan 2018

DEGREE IN MARKETING (HONS) UNIVERSITI UTARA MALAYSIA

- CGPA 3.22/4.00.
- Major in Marketing.
- School of Business Management.



July 2010 - May 2013

DIPLOMA IN MARKETING

POLITEKNIK TUANKU SULTANAH BAHIYAH

- CGPA 3.10/4.00.
- Major in Marketing.
- College of Business Management.



2010 – 2016

SEMINAR & WORKSHOP ATTENDED

POLITEKNIK TUANKU SULTANAH BAHIYAH & UNIVERSITI UTARA MALAYSIA

- Shooting Star Jabatan Perdagangan
- UniKL MSI PTSB Drama Night 2011
- POWER Seminar 2012
- Etiquette Social and protocol Course 2016

AWARDS



DEAN LIST AWARD SEM 5 (POLITEKNIK SULTANAH **BAHIYAH)**

REFERENCES

MUNIRAH KHAMARUDIN ACADEMIC LECTURER UUM

Universiti Utara Malavsia. 06010, Sintok, Kedah. Tel: +6019-442 2257 / +604-928 7486 Email: irahdin@uum.edu.my